Speaker 0: See you.
Speaker 0: Nice to see you again.
Speaker 0: What brings you back?
Speaker 1: Well, my back's been hurting again.
Speaker 0: I see.
Speaker 0: I've seen you a number of times for this, haven't I?
Speaker 1: Well, ever since I got hurt on the job three years ago, it's something that just keeps coming back.
Speaker 1: It'll be fine for a while and then I'll bend down or I'll move in a weird way and then boom, it'll just go out again.
Speaker 0: Unfortunately, that can happen.
Speaker 0: And I do have quite a few patients who get reoccurring episodes of back pain.
Speaker 0: Have you been keeping up with the therapy that we had you on before?
Speaker 1: The pills?
Speaker 0: Actually, I was talking about the physical therapy that we had you doing.
Speaker 0: The pills are only meant for short term because they don't actually prevent the back pain from coming back?
Speaker 1: Once my back started feeling better, I was happy not to go to the therapist anymore.
Speaker 1: Why was that?
Speaker 1: It was starting to become kind of a hassle.